here's what's coming up in the category
여기에 카테고리에 나오는 것이 있습니다
five TV newsroom a u.s. convenience
다섯 편의 TV 뉴스 룸
store and gas station chain had malware
상점과 주유소 체인에 악성 코드가있었습니다
that stole customer payments info for
고객 결제 정보를 훔친
more than half of 2019 if you live in
당신이 살고 있다면 2019 년의 절반 이상
the u.s. stick around you may be
우리는 당신 주위에 붙어
affected a brain implant has been
뇌 임플란트에 영향을
invented that can read people's minds
사람들의 마음을 읽을 수있는 발명품
and turn their thoughts to speech
그들의 생각을 말로 바꾸다
Amazon's ring devices were a privacy
아마존의 링 장치는 프라이버시였습니다.
nightmare in the twenty nineteen now the
스물 아홉에 악몽
company wants to improve its image by
회사는 이미지를 개선하기 위해
giving users control over their security
사용자가 자신의 보안을 제어 할 수 있도록
the company that brought us the
우리를 데려온 회사
impossible burger is now doing a
불가능한 햄버거는 이제
plant-based pork substitute as well and
식물성 돼지 고기 대용품
Google is adding new privacy and
구글은 새로운 개인 정보를 추가하고
scheduling features to their virtual
가상으로 기능 스케줄링
assistants sticker app the full details
보조 스티커 앱 전체 세부 정보
are coming up later in the show this is
쇼에서 나중에 올 것입니다.
the category five dot TV newsroom
카테고리 5 도트 TV 뉴스 룸
covering your week stop texting with a
당신의 주 중지 문자 메시지와 함께
slight linux bias
약간의 리눅스 편견
I'm
나는
sascha Rickman joined this week by Jeff
sascha Rickman은 이번 주 Jeff에 합류했습니다.
Weston and Robbie Burns made some quick
웨스턴과 로비 번즈가 좀 빨리
honorable mentions this week CES may be
이번 주 CES는
flooded with new tech coming out soon
새로운 기술이 곧 나옵니다
but it's also a great place for
그러나 그것은 또한 좋은 장소입니다
companies to show off things that
그런 것들을 과시하는 회사
they're working on that may not be
그들은 노력하지 않을 수도 있습니다
coming out to the public Dells doing
퍼블릭 델에게
just that with its Alienware gaming
Alienware 게임으로
family showing off a new concept device
새로운 개념 장치를 과시하는 가족
dubbed concept UFO it's a handheld
더빙 된 컨셉 UFO 핸드 헬드
gaming console that looks similar to a
비슷한 게임 콘솔
Nintendo switch but it's built for
닌텐도 스위치
full-fledged portable PC gaming Wow the
본격적인 휴대용 PC 게임 와우
handheld gaming console sports an 8-inch
8 인치 휴대용 게임기 스포츠
display and removable controllers on
디스플레이 및 탈착식 컨트롤러
both ends sound familiar
양쪽 끝 친숙한 소리
due to the inclusion of such a large
그런 큰 포함으로 인해
display concept UFO is in fact
디스플레이 개념 UFO는 사실
noticeably larger than a Nintendo switch
닌텐도 스위치보다 눈에 띄게 큰
and it feels bulkier from what I've been
그리고 내가 한 것보다 부피가 커집니다
told the working model arse journalist
작업 모델 엉덩이 기자에게
Valentina Palladino got to look at ran
발렌티나 팔라디노
Windows and was able to render playable
Windows는 재생 가능하게 만들 수있었습니다
games in handheld mode docked mode in
핸드 헬드 모드의 게임 도킹 모드
which a console was connected to an
콘솔이 연결된
external display and it's controllers
외부 디스플레이와 컨트롤러
were detached and another portable mode
분리되고 다른 휴대용 모드
in which the controllers were detached
컨트롤러가 분리 된 곳
but connected by a center bridge Sony
그러나 중심 교량 소니에 의해 연결
yes Sony has even demonstrated its
네, 소니도 시연했습니다
electric car concept Wow they didn't
전기 자동차 개념 와우 그들은하지 않았다
suggest that this is meant for the
이 의미는
public but rather it's being used as a
공개하지만 오히려 그것은
platform for them to demonstrate some of
그들 중 일부를 보여주는 플랫폼
their up-and-coming sensor and
그들의 다가오는 센서와
entertainment tech the vision s
엔터테인먼트 기술 비전 s
dashboard is flanked by an ultra wide
대시 보드는 매우 넓습니다.
panoramic screen for driving information
운전 정보 파노라마 화면
and entertainment combined among the
엔터테인먼트는
internal features of the car is sensing
자동차의 내부 기능이 감지됩니다
technology that can detect occupants of
탑승자를 감지 할 수있는 기술
the vehicle and even recognize them in
차량과 심지어 그들을 인식
order to allow for gesture control of
제스처 제어를 허용하기 위해
the entertainment systems in total sony
소니의 엔터테인먼트 시스템
has included 33 sensors in the vision s
비전에 33 개의 센서를 포함
prototype the Japanese firm is known to
일본 회사의 프로토 타입
have developed portable image sensors
휴대용 이미지 센서를 개발했습니다
that can be used to analyze the road in
도로를 분석하는 데 사용할 수있는
front of the vehicle as well
차량의 앞면
more from Sony it's all about Sony right
소니의 더 많은 것은 소니에 관한 것입니다.
now but the Eric's as expected the PS 5
에릭은 PS 5를 예상했지만
is shaping the future of gaming but also
게임의 미래를 형성하고 있지만
the next-generation console is inspiring
차세대 콘솔이 고무적입니다
their home cinema devices as well with
홈 시네마 기기와
Sony's newest TVs they're made
그들이 만든 소니의 최신 TV
specifically with the PS 5 in mind
특히 PS 5를 염두에두고
including its 8k resolution the flagship
8k 해상도의 주력을 포함하여
z8h can that's my Canadian pronunciation
z8h는 나의 캐나다 발음 일 수 있습니다
is it the z8h will say well stick with
z8h가 잘 붙어 있다고 말할 것입니까?
Zed Zed 8h can play at both 8k and 4k
Zed Zed 8h는 8k와 4k에서 모두 재생할 수 있습니다
with a full array LED and a built-in
전체 어레이 LED 및 내장
audio system that outputs sound based on
기반으로 사운드를 출력하는 오디오 시스템
the location of the images on screen
화면상의 이미지 위치
it's also an 85 inch screen huge whoa
그것은 또한 85 인치 스크린 거대한 와우입니다
there are some more mid-ranged LCD
더 중간 범위의 LCD가 있습니다
models in the lineup as well with five
5 개 라인업 모델
different sizes available and able to
유효한 다른 크기
support 120 Hertz 4k let's get into the
120 헤르츠 4k를 지원하자
top stories were following this week us
이번 주 주요 소식은 다음과 같습니다
convenience store Wawa recently
최근 편의점 와와
discovered malware that skimmed
감추어 진 멀웨어 발견
customers payment card data at just
고객 결제 카드 데이터
about all of its 850 stores the
약 850 개 매장 모두
infection began rolling out to the
감염이 시작되었다
stores payment processing systems on
지불 처리 시스템을 저장합니다
March 4th of last year and wasn't
작년 3 월 4 일
discovered until December the 10th it
12 월 10 일까지 발견
took two more days for malware to be
멀웨어가 되려면 이틀이 더 걸렸습니다
fully contained most locations
대부분의 위치를 ​​완전히 포함
point-of-sale systems were affected by
POS 시스템은
April 22nd 2019 although some locations
2019 년 4 월 22 일
may not have been affected at all the
전혀 영향을받지 않았을 수도 있습니다
malware collected payment card numbers
멀웨어 수집 결제 카드 번호
expiration dates and cardholder names
만료 날짜 및 카드 소지자 이름
from payment cards used at Wawa in-store
매장 내 Wawa에서 사용한 결제 카드에서
payment terminals and fuel dispensers
결제 단말기 및 연료 디스펜서
the advisory didn't say how many
권고는 얼마나 많은 말을하지 않았다
customers or cards were affected the
고객 또는 카드는
malware didn't access debit card pins
멀웨어가 직불 카드 핀에 액세스하지 못했습니다
credit card cvv2 numbers or driver
신용 카드 cvv2 번호 또는 드라이버
license data used to verify age
연령을 확인하는 데 사용되는 라이센스 데이터
restricted purchases information
제한된 구매 정보
processed by in-store ATM so it was also
매장 ATM에서 처리되었으므로
not affected the company has hired an
회사는 고용에 영향을 미치지 않습니다
outside forensic firm to investigate the
외부 법의학 회사는 조사
infection people who have used payment
지불을 사용한 감염자
cards at wawel locations
wawel 위치의 카드
should pay close attention to billing
청구에 세심한주의를 기울여야합니다
statements over the past eight months
지난 8 개월 동안의 진술
it's always a good idea to regularly
항상 정기적으로하는 것이 좋습니다
review credit report as well Wawa's said
와와의 신용 보고서 검토
it will provide one year of identity
1 년의 정체성을 제공 할 것입니다
theft protection and credit monitoring
도난 방지 및 신용 모니터링
from credit reporting service Experian
신용보고 서비스 Experian에서
at no charge hmm you get gas now you got
무료로 흠 이제 가스를 얻습니다.
to go through that yeah I can't believe
그것을 통과하려면 그래 난 믿을 수 없어
that it was active for so long before
그것은 오래 전에 활성화되었습니다
they actually I realize perhaps one year
그들은 실제로 아마 1 년을 깨달았습니다
is not long enough just say ah that's
충분하지 않아서 그냥 아
unfortunate though it is it's sad and I
안타깝지만 슬프고 나는
mean when you're traveling you don't
당신이 여행 할 때 의미하지 않는 의미
think is my information safely my dad
내 정보가 안전하게 아빠라고 생각
always said go to the same gas station
항상 같은 주유소에 가라고 말했다
all of the time that way you know if
항상 당신이 알고있는 방식으로
there's a problem you know where it came
어디서 왔는지 아는 문제가 있습니다
from
...에서
that's smart yeah yeah doesn't work if
똑똑해 그래 그래도 작동하지 않으면
you travel though no there's not the
없어도 여행하지만
brake in that case scientists have
이 경우 과학자들은 브레이크
developed a brain implant that can read
읽을 수있는 뇌 임플란트 개발
people's minds and turn their thoughts
사람들의 마음과 생각을 돌리다
into speech the team at the University
대학교에서 연설하는 팀
of California San Francisco says their
캘리포니아 샌프란시스코
findings published in the journal Nature
저널 Nature에 발표 된 결과
could help people when disease robs them
질병이 그들을 강탈 할 때 사람들을 도울 수
of their ability to talk experts said
전문가와 대화 할 수있는 능력을
the findings were compelling and offered
결과는 설득력 있고 제공되었습니다
hope of restoring speech the
연설의 회복 희망
mind-reading technology will works in
마음 읽기 기술은
two stages first an electrode is
두 단계는 먼저 전극입니다
implanted in the brain to pick up the
데리러 뇌에 이식
electrical signals that maneuver the
기동하는 전기 신호
lips tongue voice box and jaw then
입술 혀 음성 상자와 턱 다음
powerful computing is used to simulate
강력한 컴퓨팅은 시뮬레이션에 사용됩니다
how the movements in the mouth and
입안에서의 움직임과
throat would be would form different
인후는 다른 형태가 될 것입니다
sounds
소리
this results in synthesized speech
이로 인해 합성 된 음성이 생성됩니다
coming out of a virtual vocal tract
가상 성대에서 나오는
instead of scouring the brain for the
두뇌를 닦지 않고
pattern of electrical signals that code
코딩하는 전기 신호의 패턴
each word the focus is on the shape of
각 단어의 초점은
the mouth and the sounds it would
입과 소리
produce Professor Edward Chang one of
에드워드 장 교수를
the researchers said quote for the first
연구원들은 첫 번째 인용문을
time this study demonstrated that we can
이 연구는
generate an entire spoken sentences
전체 문장을 생성
based on an individual's brain activity
개인의 뇌 활동에 기초
unquote the technology is not perfect
기술이 완벽하지 않다
yet but shows incredible promise
그러나 놀라운 약속을 보여줍니다
here let's listen to an act
여기에 행동을 들어 보자
recording with the system reading its
시스템이 그것을 읽고 기록
users brainwaves and saying quote the
사용자의 뇌파와 인용문
proof you are seeking is not available
찾고있는 증거를 사용할 수 없습니다
in books the present you're seeing is
책에서 당신이보고있는 현재는
sign the livonian moves as you can hear
당신이들을 수있는 리보 니아 움직임에 서명하십시오
it's not quite perfect but keep in mind
완벽하지는 않지만 명심하십시오.
that was generated by reading someone's
누군가를 읽음으로써 생성 된
brain waves in experiments with five
다섯 실험에서 뇌파
people who read hundreds of sentences in
수백 개의 문장을 읽는 사람들
their heads listeners were able to
그들의 청취자들은
discern what was being spoken up to
무엇을 말하고 있는지 파악
seventy percent of the time
시간의 70 %
beyond helping restore speech there is
연설을 회복하는 것 외에도
also the more distant prospect of
또한 더 먼 전망
helping people who have never spoken to
말한 적이없는 사람들을 돕기
learn to speak with such a device an
그러한 장치와 대화하는 법을 배우십시오
example might be a child with cerebral
예는 뇌를 가진 아이 일 수 있습니다
palsy
바람
professor Sophie Scott from the
소피 스콧 교수
University College London said quote
유니버시티 칼리지 런던
this is very interesting work from a
이것은 매우 흥미로운 작품입니다
great lab but it must be noted that it
훌륭한 실험실이지만 주목해야합니다.
is at the very early stages and is not
초기 단계에 있고 그렇지 않습니다
close to clinical applications yet well
아직 임상 적용에 근접
you can say that but that is incredible
당신은 말할 수 있지만 그것은 믿어지지 않습니다
so like why didn't they think of this
왜 그렇게 생각하지 않았는지
before because it's like my approach to
전에는 내 접근 방식과 같기 때문에
weight loss this year is like I'm not
올해 체중 감량은 내가 아닌 것 같습니다
trying to lose weight no I'm trying to
살을 빼려고 노력하지 않아요
learn how how my body reacts to certain
내 몸이 특정 반응에 어떻게 반응하는지 배우십시오
things so similarly they're learning the
그들은 비슷하게 배우고 있습니다
the movement of the mouth right like the
바로 입의 움직임
same way like I think about like false
내가 거짓 인 것처럼 생각하는 것과 같은 방식
limbs like robotic limbs they use nerves
로봇 팔다리와 같은 사지는 신경을 사용합니다.
to actually control the hand and
실제로 손을 제어하고
everything so this is like that but
모든 것이 이렇게되어 있지만
moving of false mouth in a way to make
잘못된 입을 만드는 방법
the sounds the interesting thing about
흥미로운 점은
this though is the fact that it's using
이것은 비록 그것이 사용하고 있다는 사실입니다.
the brain signals that would go to the
뇌 신호는
mouth and voice box implies that you
입과 음성 상자는
have to have already been able to speak
이미 말할 수 있어야했다
right that's why they're saying
바로 그들이 말하는 이유입니다
eventually it will be right so I think
결국 그것은 옳을 것 같아서
it would be hard to train somebody who's
누군가를 훈련시키는 것은 어려울 것입니다
never spoken and maybe that's it yeah
말하지 않았고 어쩌면 그게 맞아
exactly so like I'm sitting there
내가 거기 앉아있는 것처럼
thinking you know you might have like a
당신은 당신이 같은 것을 알고 알고
nonverbal autistic child yes you
비언어적 자폐아
wouldn't be able to use this not the
이것을 사용할 수 없습니다
weight room that's not necessarily true
반드시 사실이 아닌 웨이트 룸
though because we don't and and there
우리가하지 않고 있기 때문에
are cases certainly where it's not going
확실하지 않은 경우입니다
to be applicable and another case would
적용 가능하고 다른 경우는
be somebody who stopped speaking because
말하기를 그만 둔 사람이 되십시오
of say brain brain dead
뇌의 뇌는 죽었다
that has affected their ability to
그들의 능력에 영향을 미쳤습니다
generate those signals so but what if
신호를 생성하지만 어떻게하면
the signal cutoff is somewhere between
신호 컷오프는
the brain and the mouth and the vocal
뇌와 입과 보컬
cords what if like I you're talking
내가 말하고있는 것이라면
about a child who can't speak well
말을 잘 못하는 아이에 대해
sometimes you'll see them moving their
때때로 당신은 그들이 움직이는 것을 볼 수 있습니다
mouth but there's no sound coming out
입이지만 소리가 나지 않습니다
and so there are cases where maybe maybe
아마도 어쩌면
the brain is sending the signal but
뇌가 신호를 보내고 있지만
maybe it's not being interpreted
어쩌면 해석되지 않을 수도 있습니다.
correctly or maybe there's a nerve
올바르게 또는 신경이있을 수 있습니다
that's not functioning correctly who
누가 제대로 작동하지 않습니다
knows right but this is a case where
잘 알고 있지만 이것은 경우입니다
it's not gonna work for it's not a
그것은 작동하지 않습니다 그것은 아닙니다
cure-all for everyone right
모두를위한 치료법
but with 70 percent accuracy this well
70 %의 정확도로
here's the thing this is the starting
여기가 시작 인 것입니다
point the starting point is 70 percent I
시작점이 70 % 인 점
can't even believe they're here I know
그들이 여기 있다는 걸 믿을 수조차 없어
it'll be interesting to see how this
이 방법을 보는 것이 재미있을 것입니다
plays into things like end-of-life care
단종 치료와 같은 일을합니다
and legal rights as far as ability to
능력까지의 법적 권리
take care of themselves I mean how many
스스로 돌봐 나는 얼마나 많은 것을 의미
people have you seen their health
사람들은 건강을 보았습니까
deteriorates and they end up in a
악화되고 그들은 결국
position where they can no longer
그들이 더 이상 할 수없는 위치
communicate but maybe muscular right but
의사 소통하지만 근육질이지만
maybe in their head they still have the
어쩌면 그들의 머리에는 여전히
ability to process those thoughts is
그 생각을 처리하는 능력은
like ALS exactly yes so that a stroke
ALS처럼 정확히 그렇습니다.
yeah totally great so cool exciting we
그래 정말 멋지다
have got to take a quick break more of
더 빨리 휴식을 취해야합니다
this week's top tech stories are coming
이번 주 최고의 기술 이야기가 올 것입니다
right up don't go anywhere
바로 아무데도 가지마
[Music]
[음악]
welcome back with criticism mounting
비판 장착으로 다시 환영
Amazon's of rape revealed a web -
아마존의 강간 웹을 공개-
dashboard of privacy controls it hopes
개인 정보 보호 제어 대시 보드
will slash the number of horror stories
공포 이야기의 수를 삭감합니다
coming from customers earlier this week
이번 주 초 고객으로부터
and in time for CES the home
그리고 CES를위한 시간에
surveillance camera an
감시 카메라
internet-connected doorbell specialists
인터넷 연결 초인종 전문가
made a point of unveiling an account
계정을 공개했다
control panel it hopes will allow users
사용자가 허용 할 수있는 제어판
to better manage the access settings on
액세스 설정을보다 잘 관리하기 위해
their devices and keep hackers and other
그들의 장치와 해커 및 기타를 유지
intruders out the new controls will be
침입자가 새로운 컨트롤을
available across all products ring said
모든 제품에서 사용 가능
in the announcement quote the control
발표에서 컨트롤을 인용
center will initially let you see and
센터는 처음에 당신을 볼 수 있습니다
manage your connected mobile desktop and
연결된 모바일 데스크톱을 관리하고
tablet devices as well as third-party
태블릿 장치 및 타사
services it will also enable you a to
그것은 또한 당신을 가능하게 할 것입니다 서비스
opt out of receiving video requests in
에서 비디오 요청 수신을 거부
areas where a local police have joined
지역 경찰이 합류 한 지역
the neighbors app end quote this comes
이웃 앱 끝 인용문이 온다
after ring found itself under fire on a
반지가 화재에서 발견 된 후
number of fronts for its privacy
개인 정보 보호를위한 전선 수
policies and security protections civil
정책 및 보안 보호 민사
rights groups have raised concerns since
권리 단체는 이후 우려를 제기했다
the cameras provide officers excessive
카메라는 장교에게 과도한 제공
levels of surveillance power in short
짧은 감 시력 수준
ring encourages its customers to share
링은 고객이 공유하도록 장려합니다
their web connected camera footage with
그들의 웹 연결 카메라 영상
neighbors and the police opening up a
이웃과 경찰은
whole can of worms regarding privacy and
프라이버시와 관련된 웜의 전체 캔
consent while it's clear there are
분명한 동안 동의
privacy concerns over cheap surveillance
저렴한 감시에 대한 개인 정보 보호 문제
devices being installed in people's
사람들에 설치되는 장치
homes hopefully the move to a user
가정은 희망적으로 사용자에게 이동
control dashboard will help improve
제어 대시 보드는 개선에 도움이됩니다
security definitely it's interesting
보안 확실히 재미있다
isn't it how these smart devices
이 똑똑한 장치가 아닌가
originally when they first started
원래 처음 시작했을 때
coming out we're taking away this
우리가 이것을 빼앗아 나오는
security control from the user so we
사용자의 보안 제어를 통해
were all having to make the assumption
모든 가정을해야했다
that our devices were secure now as
우리의 장치는 이제
we're learning no it's actually there is
우리는 실제로 그것이 없다는 것을 배우고 있습니다.
actually problems now they're saying
실제로 문제는 지금 말하는 것입니다
okay we're gonna create interfaces for
알았어 우리는 인터페이스를 만들거야
you to be able to control that security
그 보안을 제어 할 수 있도록
and they're adding features
그들은 기능을 추가하고 있습니다
and and you know there you can say smart
그리고 거기에서 당신은 똑똑하다고 말할 수 있습니다.
devices and connected devices are a bad
장치 및 연결된 장치가 불량
thing well they're probably not they're
잘 그들은 아마 그들이 아니에요
just young and I think we do have to
젊고 우리가해야 할 것 같아
give some grace to the companies that
회사에 은혜를 베풀어
are manufacturing them because they are
그들이 있기 때문에 제조하고 있습니다
they're learning from their mistakes and
그들은 자신의 실수에서 배우고
I think they're they're proving the to
나는 그들이 그것을 증명하고 있다고 생각
that they're making changes based on
그들이 기반으로 변경하고 있다는
those mistakes I heard one argument that
그 실수는
well it doesn't enforce two-factor
물론 그것은 두 가지 요소를 강요하지 않습니다
authentication by default and I thought
기본적으로 인증하고 생각
wow what today it doesn't force
와우 오늘은 강요하지 않는 것
two-factor authentication and I set up a
이중 인증 및 나는
bank account with my bank this week and
이번 주 내 은행에 은행 계좌
they gave me online banking and they
그들은 온라인 뱅킹을했고
didn't enforce two-factor authentication
이중 인증을 시행하지 않았습니다
talked into it right
바로 이야기했다
the bank didn't do it so yeah we're
은행은 그렇게하지 않았다 그래, 우리는
being really hard on a new platform for
새로운 플랫폼에서 정말 열심히
the very same thing that the bank here
여기 은행과 똑같은
in Canada like I'm not talking TD Canada
내가 TD 캐나다를 말하지 않는 것처럼 캐나다에서
Trust like a big bank they don't enforce
그들이 시행하지 않는 큰 은행처럼 신뢰
either right so so we got to put things
어느 쪽이든 그래서 우리는 물건을 넣어야
into context but yes I think it's a good
상황에 맞지만 그래, 나는 그것이 좋은 생각
thing that companies are starting to
회사가 시작하는 것
respond to their users and I think it's
그들의 사용자에게 응답하고 나는 생각
kind of neat that they're creating a
그들이 만드는 깔끔한 종류
capability for law enforcement to
법 집행 능력
utilize neighborhood cameras I remember
내가 기억하는 동네 카메라 활용
there was a car accident
교통 사고가 있었다
in the summer someone driving a Tesla at
여름에 누군가가 테슬라를 운전
top speed hit a hill and crashed it
최고 속도는 언덕을 명중하고 추락
remember that yes I do and the police
그래, 내가하고 경찰을 기억
were able to tap into a surveillance
감시에 활용할 수 있었다
camera on a house nearby
근처 집에 카메라
they saw the entire accident like that's
그들은 전체 사고를
cool we wouldn't want our privacy
우리는 우리의 개인 정보를 원하지 않을 것
violated that's the thing we have to
우리가해야 할 일을 위반했습니다
find the line and I think having control
줄을 찾아 제어 할 생각
and being able to say okay the the one
그리고 하나는 괜찮아 말할 수
in my garage is mine yeah the one that's
내 차고 안에는 내 꺼야
pointed at the street you can you can
당신이 할 수있는 거리를 지적
you can have access to that yeah you
당신은 그것에 접근 할 수 있습니다
know just having a certain level of user
특정 수준의 사용자가 있다는 것을 알고
control is a good thing interesting you
제어는 당신에게 흥미로운 좋은 것입니다
know Mike nope just to stop new year new
새해를 막기 위해 Mike nope를 아는 것
decade
열개의
oh is this is this your resolution I
아이게 네 해상도 야
like it
그 것처럼
right a plant-based pork substitute has
바로 식물성 돼지 고기 대용품이
been launched at CES by one of the
CES에서
leading alternative meat producers a
대체 대체 육류 생산 업체
food product unveiled at the CES tech
CES 기술에 공개 된 식품
show you betcha there's some serious
진지하게 보여줘
tech involved in creating this
이것을 만드는 데 관련된 기술
sustainable alternative to meat the new
새로운 육류에 대한 지속 가능한 대안
product contains no gluten animal
제품은 글루텐 동물을 포함하지 않습니다
hormones or antibiotics and is designed
호르몬 또는 항생제이며
to comply with kosher and halal rules
코셔 및 할랄 규칙 준수
the firm's sausage and plant-based pork
회사의 소시지와 식물성 돼지 고기
products a similar to ground beef
갈은 소고기와 유사한 제품
substitute are made using heme a
헴을 사용하여 대체됩니다
molecule derived from plants that
식물에서 추출한 분자
contains iron and resembles blood heme
철분을 함유하고 혈액 헴과 유사
is found in real meat but can be
진짜 고기에서 발견되지만
produced without farming animals
농사를 짓지 않고 생산
impossible Foods founder and chief
불가능한 음식 설립자 및 최고
executive Patrick Brown says they're
패트릭 브라운 중역은
expanding products of size of their
그들의 크기의 제품을 확장
extended expanding product line quote we
확장 된 제품 라인 견적
won't stop until we eliminate the need
우리가 필요를 제거 할 때까지 멈추지 않을 것입니다
for our animals in the food chain and
먹이 사슬에있는 동물들에게
make the global food system sustainable
글로벌 식품 시스템을 지속 가능하게
and close beyond that impossible pork
그 불가능한 돼지 고기를 넘어서
contains around half the calories of
칼로리의 약 절반을 포함
sausage meat and is also significantly
소시지 고기 또한 크게
lower in fat until recently China was
최근까지 중국의 지방 감소
home to around half the world's farmed
전 세계 농민의 반 정도의 고향
pigs but millions of them have died or
돼지이지만 수백만 마리가 죽었거나
been cold due to the spread of the
의 확산으로 추위
African swine fever a viral disease that
아프리카 돼지 열병 바이러스 성 질병
infects pigs and has no known cure pork
돼지를 감염시키고 알려진 치료 돼지 고기가 없습니다.
is Hugh in huge demand in Asia China
아시아 중국에서 엄청난 수요가 있습니다
alone produces and consumes more of the
혼자서 더 많은 것을 생산하고 소비합니다
meat than any other country impossible
다른 어떤 나라보다도 고기
foods say that there isn't that
음식은 그렇지 않다고 말합니다
synthetic pork product will suit a
합성 돼지 고기 제품은
variety of Asian dishes that's
다양한 아시아 요리
interesting we're we're at that point
우리가 그 시점에있어 흥미로운
where like I think I said on a show
내가 쇼에서 말했다 생각
years ago
여러 해 전에
won't it be neat when they can
그들이 할 수있을 때 깔끔하지 않습니까
synthesize right and they're here they
바로 합성하고 그들이 여기 있습니다
are in that that tricky little spot
그 까다로운 작은 자리에
where they're just about to tip right
그들이 바로 팁하려고하는 곳
over into a mold synthesize station I
금형 합성 스테이션 I에
can't speak but but what's weird about
말할 수는 없지만 이상한 점은
it
그것
from a technology standpoint is that
기술적 인 관점에서 보면
it's like meat like it's not like ground
그것은 지상과 같지 않은 고기와 같습니다
mushrooms
버섯
held together with gluten right that's
글루텐과 함께 개최
where I have a hard time so I don't eat
힘든 시간을 보내서 먹지 않는 곳
meat but I don't eat meat because I
고기지만 고기를 먹지 않아서
don't like meat and so I like
고기를 좋아하지 않아서
so that's different from the ethical our
윤리적 윤리와는 다릅니다
sustainability perfectly whereas like
완벽하게 지속 가능성
people who want to eat healthier or want
더 건강하게 먹고 싶어하는 사람들
to hmm
흠
to tread light or happy that all of
빛을 밟거나
those things are happening in my life
내 인생에서 일어나는 일들
but that's not the reason I don't eat
하지만 내가 안 먹는 이유는 아니에요
meat okay so once they're able to do
그들이 할 수 있으면 고기 좋아
bacon I think that that's the point when
베이컨 그 시점이 그 시점이라고 생각합니다
everybody in this whole world is going
이 세상의 모든 사람들이 가고 있습니다
to be like and everyone who says but
같은 사람과 말하지만
they have vegetarian bacon but it's not
그들은 채식 베이컨을 가지고 있지만
I can tell you that because I like the
내가 좋아하기 때문에
vegetarian bacon and I don't like bacon
채식 베이컨 저는 베이컨을 좋아하지 않습니다
so that means no I do like I on the
그래서 나는 내가 좋아하지 않는다는 것을 의미합니다.
other hand eat meat yeah yeah but but
다른 손은 고기를 먹습니다
I've tasted a lot of these alternatives
나는이 많은 대안들을 맛 보았다
yeah have you tried the impossible
그래, 불가능을 시도 했니
burger does anyone sell it yes plenty of
버거는 누구나 많이 팔아요
places including grocery stores and is
식료품 점을 포함하여
there any restaurant example I think
내가 생각하는 레스토랑 예가 있습니다.
then what's the one I think the one that
그때 내가 생각하는 것은 무엇입니까
I've tried is beyond burger not
나는 시도 버거 넘어
impossible perhaps that's why they end
불가능할 수도 있습니다.
up yours yeah and W has them have you
너를 위로하고 W는 너를 가지고있어.
tried it
그것을 시도
mm-hmm and it was good but it was
흠 그리고 그것은 좋았지 만
tougher than beef they didn't have a
그들은 쇠고기보다 강하다
nice soft like beef tenderness it was
쇠고기 부드러움처럼 부드럽고 부드럽습니다.
tougher like it seemed gluttonous to me
그것이 나에게 영양가처럼 보였다
okay so with that so I yeah it was good
그래, 그래도 좋았어
but I wouldn't go out of my way to buy
그러나 나는 내 구매 방식을 벗어나지 않을 것입니다
it personally but if you were a
개인적으로 그러나 당신이
vegetarian or a vegan and they did an
채식인이나 비건 채식인과
alternative then that's a reasonable
대안은 합리적입니다
alternative and I mean if in China
대안과 나는 중국에 있다면
they're having a big pork shortage this
그들은 큰 돼지 고기 부족이있다
is it and they use full flavor dishes
그것과 그들은 전체 풍미 요리를 사용
right so I think that really just
맞아요 그래서 정말
membership mimicking the texture is
질감을 흉내 낸 멤버쉽은
probably all it's not always needed like
아마 항상 필요한 것은 아닙니다
I mean if you have some soup and you
수프가 있다면
want to just have like a couple of meaty
그냥 고기 같은 커플을 갖고 싶어
chunks in it like throw in some pork
돼지 고기를 던지는 것처럼 덩어리
alternative whatever what I want to know
내가 알고 싶은 것이 무엇이든 대안
though is how did it end up at CES
CES에서 어떻게 끝났습니까?
because of the technology right what
기술로 인해
tech no like I want to know me
내가 아는 것 같은 기술은 없다
on me no mean I'd like it meat good
나에게 고기가 좋겠다는 뜻은 아니야
bacon good how you do that how did you
베이컨 잘 했어 어떻게 그렇게 했니
exactly like what is it about the tack
압정에 대해 정확히 무엇입니까
that makes this happen because Jeff they
제프 때문에
clearly it's science there's a tech that
분명히 과학입니다 기술은
pulls a specific thing out of plants
식물에서 특정 것을 꺼내다
that is produced by the same thing that
그것은 같은 것과 같은 것에 의해 생성됩니다
comes out of meat like that and it's
그런 고기에서 나오고
like they're creating synthetic meat
합성 고기를 만드는 것처럼
from plants what happens but it's that's
식물에서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있지만 그것은
what I mean by it's different from
내가 의미하는 바는
ground-up vegetables right together with
vegetables은 야채와 함께
glue it's not like texturized vegetable
텍스쳐 화 된 야채와 달라요
no it's like it's like me it's like in a
아니 그것은 마치 나처럼
lot of ways like it's very very similar
매우 비슷한 방식으로
that's where I that's where they're
그것이 내가있는 곳입니다.
getting to that point I still want real
그 시점에 도달하고 난 여전히 진짜를 원한다
bacon it's like the petri dish that this
베이컨이게 페트리 접시 같아요
is not but like when we've talked about
우리가 얘기했을 때와는 다릅니다
the petri dish meat that is grown in a
에서 자란 페트리 접시 고기
dish that has never actually been an
실제로 적이없는 요리
animal yeah it totally does from a
동물 그래, 그것은 완전히
sustainability standpoint though I do
비록 지속 가능성 관점
understand that there's too much factory
공장이 너무 많다는 것을 이해
farming going on I understand that yeah
농업은 계속 이해합니다 그래
and you know for health sake I'm gonna
그리고 건강을 위해 내가 할거야
like eat healthier I'm not I'm still
더 건강하게 먹는 것처럼 나는 아직도 아니에요
eating meat but I'm not eating as much
고기를 먹지만 많이 먹지 않아요
right of unhealthy stuff I just don't
건강에 해로운 것들의 권리
cook my eggs on my bacon grease anymore
더 이상 베이컨 그리스에 계란을 요리하십시오
healthier perfect Tuesday all of the new
건강하고 완벽한 화요일 모든 새로운
capabilities it's added to its voice
음성에 추가 된 기능
assistant including various additions to
다양한 추가를 포함한 조수
the way it handles privacy one of these
그것이 개인 정보를 처리하는 방식 중 하나
systems new privacy features will allow
새로운 개인 정보 보호 기능을 통해
users to delete a record of the most
사용자는 가장 기록을 삭제
recent command by saying that wasn't for
그것이 아니었다 고 말함으로써 최근 명령
you
당신
this means users can delete voice
이것은 사용자가 음성을 삭제할 수 있음을 의미합니다
recordings immediately if someone else
다른 사람이 있으면 즉시 녹음
starts at the separate conversation in
별도의 대화에서 시작
the background or if the user decides
배경 또는 사용자가 결정하는 경우
that what was said should not be shared
말한 내용을 공유해서는 안된다
users can also ask are you saving my
사용자는 또한 당신이 내 저장 저장 요청할 수 있습니다
audio data to learn more about their
오디오 데이터에 대한 자세한 내용
privacy controls and to go directly to
개인 정보 보호 및
the settings screen to change their
설정 화면을 변경하여
preferences as well as delete voice
환경 설정 및 음성 삭제
assistant activity from a Google account
Google 계정의 보조 활동
by saying things like quote delete
인용 삭제와 같은 것을 말함으로써
everything I said to you this week the
이번 주에 내가 말한 모든 것
assistant has had a fair share of
조수는
privacy concerns with Google confirming
Google의 개인 정보 보호 문제 확인
in August that third-party
8 월에 타사
kurz were systematically listening
kurz는 체계적으로 듣고있었습니다
systematically listening and linking
체계적으로 듣고 연결하기
private touch conversations collected by
에 의해 수집 된 개인 터치 대화
the assistance it had been revealed that
그 도움이 밝혀졌다
more than 1,000 files had been leaked
1,000 개가 넘는 파일이 유출되었습니다
from these workers including recordings
녹음을 포함하여이 근로자들로부터
of from instances where users
사용자가있는 인스턴스 중
accidentally triggered Google's software
실수로 Google 소프트웨어를 트리거
after the incident a google paused all
사건 후 구글은 모두 일시 중지
of its language for a few operations
몇 가지 작업에 대한 언어
these new privacy features common not
이 새로운 개인 정보 보호 기능은 일반적이지 않습니다
too long after Google decided to revamp
구글이 개조하기로 결정한지 너무 오래
its assistant privacy policy last year
작년 보조 개인 정보 보호 정책
the changes from last year included
작년의 변화는 포함
Google making it default for the voice
음성으로 기본 설정하는 Google
assistant to not retain audio recordings
오디오 녹음을 유지하지 않는 보조
a once a request is fulfilled meaning
일단 요청이 이행되면 의미
that users have to opt in to let Google
사용자가 Google을 사용하도록 선택해야합니다.
keep any voice recordings made by the
에 의해 음성 녹음을 유지
device it also added a feature that
장치는 또한 기능을 추가
allows users to review and delete past
사용자가 과거를 검토하고 삭제할 수 있습니다
historical audio recordings besides the
게다가 역사적인 오디오 녹음
security enhancements other additions to
보안 개선 사항
the assistant announced by Google on
Google에서 발표 한 조수
Tuesday include the ability to schedule
화요일에는 스케줄 기능이 포함됩니다
certain tasks for example users that
특정 작업 (예 : 사용자)
have a Google home integrated washer or
Google 홈 통합 세탁기가 있거나
dryer can schedule a load of laundry
건조기는 세탁물을 예약 할 수 있습니다
with the assistant this feature is set
보조자와 함께이 기능이 설정됩니다
to be rolled out later this year Google
올해 말 구글 출시 예정
has added support for various new smart
다양한 새로운 스마트에 대한 지원을 추가했습니다
devices categories such as AC units
AC 장치와 같은 장치 범주
coffee makers vacuums and smart bathtubs
커피 메이커 진공 청소기와 스마트 욕조
among others I would love for my device
무엇보다도 나는 내 장치를 좋아합니다
to be able to make me good coffee oh and
나에게 좋은 커피를 만들 수 있도록
bring it to me I would like to be able
나에게 가져다 줄 수 있기를 바란다
to run a bath I don't know about the
내가 모르는 목욕을 실행
bath thing and I don't know about the
목욕 물건과 나는 모른다
anything with water bath and laundry
수조와 세탁물이있는 물건
I think I'm against I think it would be
내가 반대하는 것 같아
cool I know that my neighbor down the
멋진 내 이웃을 알고
street has one of the new like washer
거리에는 세탁기와 같은 새로운 세탁기 중 하나가 있습니다
and dryer in one machine yep right so if
그리고 하나의 기계에 건조기가 있습니다.
you put a load of wash in but you know
세탁물을 많이 넣었지만
that you're gonna be home from work at a
직장에서 집에있을 거라는
certain time yes that stuff to be not
특정 시간 예 그 물건은
wrinkly just sitting there then you
주름이 그냥 거기 앉아
could like time one into your home scene
시간을 당신의 가정 장면에 넣을 수 있습니다
I'm the guy who has had pipes break and
나는 파이프가 끊어진 사람이고
had right things like that happened so
그런 일이 옳았어요
for me it's like I monitor things like I
나를 위해 내가 같은 것을 모니터링하는 것
check on the laundry while it's
세탁물을 확인하면서
happening
사고
right I check on the lot the dishwasher
오른쪽 식기 세척기를 많이 확인합니다
while it's happening I don't run them
그것이 일어나는 동안 나는 그들을 실행하지 않습니다
when I'm not home I super trust me yeah
내가 집에 없을 때 나는 나를 믿어
my dad had it happen where the laundry
아빠가 세탁소에서 일어나셨어요
machine started spraying water all over
기계가 물을 뿌리기 시작했습니다
and they didn't know and it just
그들은 몰랐고 그냥
destroyed their basement so it's just
지하실을 파괴해서 그냥
like yeah I'm not for that but make me a
그래 그래 난 아니에요하지만 나를 만들
coffee yeah that beer and bring it to me
커피 그래 그 맥주와 나에게 가져
what I find interesting about this story
내가이 이야기에서 흥미로운 것을 발견 한
is that it's go yeah the stories it's
그것은 간다 그래 그래 그것은 이야기
Google and they're making changes toward
구글과 그들은 향해 변화하고 있습니다
users being able to control their
사용자가 자신을 제어 할 수있는
privacy once again right but it's
프라이버시를 다시 한 번 제대로하지만
interesting that Google kind of missed
구글의 종류가 그리워 흥미로운
the boat on this initially I feel like
이 보트는 처음에
Google has kind of always been ahead of
구글은 항상 앞서있다
the game when it comes to that respect
그 존중에 관한 게임
for privacy because they've kind of been
그들은 일종의 개인 정보 보호를 위해
the front-runner mm-hmm
선두 주자 mm-hmm
so the fact that they're trying to play
그들이 플레이하려고한다는 사실은
catch-up now and the fact that there was
지금 따라 잡기와 거기에 있었던 사실
audio breaches where conversations were
대화가 있었던 오디오 위반
being shared I'm going wow Google come
공유되고 나는 Google 와우
on yeah but I mean it's good to see that
그래,하지만 나는 그것을 보는 것이 좋다는 것을 의미한다
they're making these changes you know
그들은 당신이 알고있는 이러한 변화를하고있다
but it's all of us think everybody's
하지만 우리 모두는 모두의 생각
learning right including Google
구글을 포함한 학습 권리
obviously listen this is why I don't let
분명히 이것이 내가 못하게하는 이유입니다.
anyone else do anything and I do I'm
다른 사람이 뭐든지하고 난 해요
terrible at delegating because I'm
내가 있기 때문에 위임에 끔찍한
afraid of someone making mistakes and so
누군가 실수하는 것을 두려워해서
they've hired a third party company or
타사를 고용했거나
maybe they had staff that was doing this
아마 그들은이 일을하는 직원이 있었을 것입니다
job and that staff leaked the
직업과 그 직원 유출
information yep yes that was meant to be
정보 그래 그래 그 예정이었다
internal like we need to improve our
우리가 개선해야 할 것처럼 내부
product now I have an Amazon device at
이제 제품에 아마존 장치가 있습니다.
home mm-hmm
가정 mm-hmm
ditto so these features like that wasn't
그와 같은 기능은 그렇지 않았습니다.
meant for you and stuff mm-hmm are their
당신을 위해 의미하고 mm-hmm은 그들의
equivalents on the Amazon devices I'm
내가 사용하는 Amazon 기기의 해당 제품
seeing very similar kinds of
매우 비슷한 종류의
enhancements happening okay
괜찮은 개선
Amazon and you know I've talked about it
아마존과 당신은 내가 그것에 대해 이야기를 알고
before but the Amazon echo I have mine
전에는 아마존 반향이 있습니다
set in the app to make a tone any time
앱에서 언제든지 소리를 내도록 설정
it hears its activity outward and so
활동이 바깥으로 들리므로
sometimes you'll hear me if if it goes
간혹 들리면 가끔 듣습니다
off here I just say cancel so in the
여기서는 그냥 취소라고 말합니다.
middle of a conversation somebody says
누군가 대화의 중간에
that the action word by accident and I
우연히 그 행동 단어와
hear DubLi and I say cancel and it just
DubLi를 듣고 취소라고 말하면
now it comes naturally so right and I
이제 자연스럽게옵니다
wish sometimes it will work in real life
때로는 현실에서 작동하기를 바랍니다.
conversations with humans I convinced
내가 설득 한 인간과의 대화
our kids that ours is now Hansel gecko
우리 아이들은 이제 헨젤 도마뱀입니다
yes you can change your what no because
네 당신은 무엇을 변경할 수 없습니다
o because we chose echo yeah as the as
우리는 에코를 선택 했으니 까
the name Oh
이름 아
but because you've got gecko I convinced
하지만 당신은 내가 도마뱀을 가지고 있기 때문에
my kids to call it gecko nice oh my god
내 아이들이 그것을 게코라고 불러
changed the name to get girls are the
여자가 얻을 수 있도록 이름을 변경
like gecko that's cool
멋진 도마뱀처럼
big thanks to Roy W Nash and our
Roy W Nash와 우리에게 큰 감사
community of yours for submitting
제출을위한 귀하의 커뮤니티
stories to us this week thanks for
이번 주 우리에게 이야기
watching the category-five TV newsroom
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스 룸 시청
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
좋아하고 구독하는 것을 잊지 마세요
all your tech news with a slight linux
약간의 리눅스로 모든 기술 뉴스
bias and for if you appreciate what we
우리가 무엇을 좋아하는지에 대한 편견과
do become a patron at patreon.com slash
patreon.com 슬래시에서 후원자가 되십시오
news herb from the category five dots of
카테고리에서 다섯 가지 뉴스 허브
a newsroom I'm Sasha Bergman I'm Robbie
뉴스 룸 저는 Sasha Bergman입니다. Robbie입니다.
Ferguson and I'm Jeff Lester
퍼거슨과 저는 제프 레스터입니다